[speaker=none]*knock on door*
[speaker=none]*footsteps*
[speaker=none]*door opens*
Oh… hi.
I wasn’t expecting you.
[speaker=Neighbor]I just wanted to check in.
How’s she doing?
Back at the hospital again.
They’re trying something new… but…
*sigh* It’s just getting harder to pretend, you know?
[speaker=Neighbor]She’s a fighter.
Yeah. That’s what they all say.
Fighters.
Like that makes a difference.
I don’t even know who I am when she’s not here.
But when she is… it’s worse.
I’m supposed to be strong.
For her. For him.
But I’m…
I’m breaking too.
And there’s no one left to lean on.
[speaker=Neighbor]You don’t have to do this alone.
…Yeah. Maybe I don’t.
[speaker=none]*rustling sounds*
[speaker=Neighbor]If you need anything at all…
I’m here.
[speaker=none]*door closes*
I just hope… it’s the last time.